ambitenergy.com 2009-12-31

# Ambit

Ambit Energy, L.P.’s Privacy Policy
Our Companywide Privacy Commitment to You
As an internet user, we understand how important safeguarding your personal information is to you. At Ambit Energy, L.P., we are committed to protecting your personal
information as you use our website.
We would like to take this opportunity to let you know that Ambit Energy, L.P. does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone unless such information is
provided to us voluntarily and knowingly except as otherwise provided in this Policy. We only collect personal information for specific purposes, including providing you with
retail energy service. We will not sell or make available your personal information to unaffiliated companies for commercial purposes unrelated to the business of Ambit Energy,
L.P. However, we may use this information to inform you of goods or services that may interest you. Ambit Energy, L.P. will not disclose any information about you to
unaffiliated companies or organizations without your consent except as disclosed to you in this Policy, unless: (a) we are required to do so by law; (b) we believe it necessary to
respond to an inquiry or provide you with a requested service; (c) It is necessary to make good on our Terms of Service Agreement we have entered into with you; or (d) to
protect the rights, property or personal safety of any other person, including another Ambit Energy, L.P customer or any member of the public.
Ambit Energy, L.P. and its affiliates recognize that by utilizing our website you are placing trust in us. We thank you. Let us assure you that we will take precautions to protect
your information. In order to operate the Website and deliver retail electric service we may share your personal information with a service partner under strict conditions. We
will not otherwise disclose your personal information to other companies without your explicit consent.
You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view a large majority of our site. However, to obtain services from Ambit Energy, L.P. or to access
portions of our Website, including, but not limited to, Ambit Energy, L.P.'s “Power Zone”, “My Energy Account” or other services provided by Ambit Energy, L.P., you may be
asked to provide personal information. We use your information to personalize your Web experience or to provide you with requested services. Ambit Energy, L.P. will only use
your information strictly in accordance with this Policy.
How We Protect Your Information
Ambit Energy, L.P. will endeavor to take all steps deemed reasonable by Ambit Energy, L.P. to keep secure any information we hold about you, and to keep this information
accurate and current. Your information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. We require our employees and data processors to respect the
confidentiality of any personal information held by Ambit Energy, L.P. Ambit Energy takes many precautions, including administrative and technical measure, to protect your
personal information against theft, mishandling and loss. Additionally, Ambit protects against misuse of your information, such as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration,
and destruction of your personal information. No one, including Ambit Energy, can give absolute assurance that your information will be secure 100% of the time due to the
nature of the internet. Ambit Energy, L.P. will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information.
Ambit Energy, L.P. uses appropriate commercially available anti‐virus software to ensure that this Website does not contain or carry viruses. However, due to the rapidly
developing nature of viruses and the Internet we strongly recommend that you employ similar anti‐virus software when accessing the Ambit Energy, L.P. Website. Ambit Energy,
L.P. makes no warranty that the Website or e‐mail correspondence is free from such viruses.
Children
Our Website contains educational energy‐related information that may be of interest to children. Ambit Energy, L.P. does not seek to gather personal information online from or
about children under the age of 13. Ambit Energy, L.P. encourages all children and young teens to ask their parents for authorization before providing any information about
themselves or their household to anyone over the Internet.
Data Collection
Ambit may use "cookie" technology on our Website. "Cookies" are small text files a Website can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's access to and use of the site
and to track behavior of the Web pages you visit, among other uses. Our Website may automatically collect Cookies and other information, including, but not limited to, your
domain name, and Ambit may compile aggregate data for statistical purposes to improve our content of our website or to better administer the web pages available on the
Ambit Energy Website.
When and if Ambit Energy requests an email address from you, you will be given the opportunity to indicate whether or not you wish to receive future email solicitations from
us. Regardless, from time to time we may send you emails for other reasons, including, but not limited to servicing your energy account with us.
Privacy Questions
This Website is owned and operated by Ambit Energy, LP. This Privacy Policy is to provide you with assurance and explain Ambit’s policy to ensure you personal information is
protected and properly used. If you have questions about this Policy, please feel free to e‐mail us at compliance@ambitenergy.com or write us at:
Ambit Energy, LP
1801 N. Lamar Ste 200
Dallas, TX 75202
Attn: Compliance Department
If you would like to know what information Ambit retains or if you wish to have Ambit change your information because it is out of date or inaccurate, please contact us by e‐
mail at compliance@ambitenergy.com and we will modify your record accordingly.
Last updated November 4, 2008 © 2008 Ambit Energy, L.P. All rights reserved.
